KERRI-ANN BATES

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

🖿 bates.kerriann@gmail.com 📞 407-790-8467 👂 Orlando, Fl 🛮 in kerri-ann-bates-0b4970129/ 🗘 Kerri-AnnBates

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer focused on modern technology, maintainability, and goal driven work in a team environment. Prior experience includes 2+ years in frontend development working on responsive maintenance and content management. In addition, 4+ years in accounts receivable providing excellent customer service and managing numerous accounts has taught me communication and management skills to succeed on a collaborative team.

EMPLOYMENT

Nov. 2017 to Current

The Storage Group · Web Developer · Altamonte Springs, Fl

- Perform quality assurance checks on approximately 2-3 websites per week.
- · Build upon CMS themed websites using HTML and CSS
- Create responsive layouts implementing media queries
- Perform tests on different browsers with browser testing tool

July 2013 to Nov. 2017

Katsur Management · Accounts Receivable Representative · Altamonte Springs, Fl

- Managed up to 300+ client accounts a month
- Providing excellent customer service to clients
- Accurate data entry
- Data analysis

EDUCATION

Sept. 2019 to Current

Lambda School

2020

Certificate Full-Stack Development

9+ month Computer Science & Software Engineering Academy that provides hands-on curriculum focusing on web and mobile development, and computer science.

2015 to 2019

Seminole State College

2019

Associates Degree Computer Programming

SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, React.js, HTML, CSS, Sass, Redux, Node, Express.js, SQLite, Git, API, JSON

PROJECTS

Jan. 2020 to Mar.

Alpava Vids

2020

A video journal web application that allow users to practice answering prompt questions by recording themselves answering those questions and receiving feedback from their team members on one platform. Worked with a remote team of 4 full-stack developers and 1 UX designer over 2 months.

- Functioned as a full-stack developer
- Created several API endpoints, a protective middleware, and tests for those endpoints on the backend using jest, node, express and knex
- · Worked with Postgres relational database
- Created responsive base layout with Sass
- Created actions in redux, dispatching data from endpoints to display on the frontend
- Implemented CRUD operations